netflights.com 2011-10-07

# netflights.com privacy and legal policy

### Information we may collect about you

When using this website you might be asked for some personal information. You are free to decide whether you will give this information to us, but be aware that some of the services we offer may not be available if you do not supply the information requested.

We might request personal information in the following circumstances:

When you purchase or reserve a product with us; submit a product enquiry to us; provide us with feedback about our website; request a brochure from us; register to receive emails about our products and special offers; take part in one of our online surveys or apply for a job.

### Bookings, Product and Special Offers

When you book with netflights.com you are registering to receive product information from us. We will hold your postal and email addresses to send you information regarding our products and special offers. You can choose to opt out of our mailing list at any time by using the unsubscribe link in any email you receive or by emailing your address details to [optout@goldmedal.co.uk](mailto:optout@goldmedal.co.uk).

### Computer information

We may collect technical information about your computer when you visit our web site. This may include your IP address, operating system, web browser software, screen resolution and referring web site.

We do not link any of this computer information to any personal information we hold about you. This information is used purely to ensure our web site is built to provide the best experience for you.

### How we use this information:

#### To fulfil booking requests

When you book or reserve a product with us we will hold the information you submit to process, administer and account for your booking. You should expect to receive an email confirmation from us shortly after you complete your booking or reservation. We might call you, if necessary, to fulfil the service offered to you.

The information you provide may be passed to third parties as necessary to provide the services requested. These third parties may be located outside of the UK.

#### Product enquiries

If you submit a product enquiry to us using one of the forms on the website, we will use this information to produce a quotation for you. You will then receive an email or a phone call as a follow up to a product enquiry.

#### Feedback and surveys

If you submit feedback to us regarding our services, then we will use the information submitted to improve our services. We might contact you by email or phone to discuss any feedback that you provide.

If you volunteer to take part in a survey on our web site, any information collected will only be used for statistical purposes. You personal information will not be identifiable from the results of any survey.

#### Brochure requests

The information you submit for a brochure request is used solely for this purpose. The information you supply is sent to a third party, AU Marketing Services, who manage the distribution of brochures on our behalf. They do not use this information for any other purposes - you won't receive anything you didn't ask for.

#### Product and special offer emails

If you register to receive product emails from us you can expect to receive emails regarding all of our travel services and products. The details you submit to receive this information is not used for any other purpose and will not be shared with any third parties.

### Is your information secure?

We take great care in ensuring that any personal information you submit is secure and held securely. The information you submit will only be used for the purposes described in this privacy & security policy.

### Information you submit to our website

All information you provide to netflights.com is transmitted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt or scramble data before you send it to us.

### Electronic links to third parties

All credit card details are passed through a dedicated secure link to our bank for payment processing. We may pass any personal information to a third party electronically to fulfil a booking request; this will always be via a secure link.

### Internet security

All of your details are held securely in the netflights.com computer systems. These are protected from the Internet by industry standard firewalls and several layers of Internet security and virus protection.

### Emails are not secure

Any information emailed between you and netflights.com will be via standard email methods. This is not encrypted and you should be careful about placing personal information in an email. We would advise you to never place your credit card details in an email and we will never ask you to do so.

### Cookies

This website makes use of cookies. In order to help us maintain and improve our service to you netflights.com also uses 'cookies' to collect information about your use of the website. Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to temporarily store information within your browser, which in turn allows us to recognise the computer used to access netflights.com. Most browsers automatically accept cookies but you can delete existing cookies from your browser. You can also edit your browser options to choose not to receive cookies in future. We may use cookies to keep track of the transaction from one page to the next.

#### Session cookies

These are used to maintain something called session state. Session cookies are required for the website to function but are not used in any way to identify you personally.

#### Permanent cookies

When you visit netflights.com, we will assign a permanent cookie on the hard drive of your computer. You can view these by looking in the cookies directory of your browser installation. As the name implies, permanent cookies last for a long time and each time you visit our website you send us a copy of them allowing us to identify you from visit to visit. The aim is to enhance your experience whilst on the website and make sure you don’t miss out on great offers. Cookies do not contain any Personal Information for example, your name, address, email address, or telephone number, but simply a unique identification number that identifies your computer to us.

#### Opting out

Although you cannot block "session" cookies as they are required for our website to function correctly you can configure your Internet browser so that it can reject both "permanent" and "third party" cookies. How you do this will depend upon the Internet browser you. Please refer to the relevant Internet browser manufacturer's website where you should be able to receive all the information you need.

### Other web sites

We provide links to related websites throughout our website. These are placed here for your convenience. You should be aware that content or information provided on these third party websites is not the responsibility of the netflights.com and is not covered by this Privacy & Security policy.

### Job applications

Any information you send in response to a job advertisement is used solely for recruitment purposes. We might contact you by phone or via email in relation to any job applications you make. The personal information you submit will not be used for any other purposes.

### Can we change this policy?

Netflights.com reserves the right to change and amend this policy for any reason. The policy which was in place at the time you submitted information to us will apply.

### Feedback, comments and suggestions

Netflights.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy, as well as any other aspect of our service.

If you would like to contact netflights.com regarding this policy, please send you enquiry by email to [optout@goldmedal.co.uk](mailto:optout@goldmedal.co.uk).

This policy was produced on 18th May 2011.

Netflights.com is a trading name of Airline Network Plc, a company registered in England under company No: 2624338 and having its registered office address at The Trident Centre, Port Way, Ribble Docklands, Preston, Lancashire, PR2 2QG, UK. VAT Registration No. 732854915
